freesex.com 2010-10-07

# Contact Us FreeSex.com: FreeSex, Free Sex, Free Porn, Free Sex videos

**FREESEX.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

This FreeSex.com Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") discloses the privacy practices for us at FreeSex.com ("FreeSex") and how we treat the information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of FreeSex products and services. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that FreeSex does not own or control or to people that FreeSex does not employ or manage. By visiting this website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access the FreeSex.com website.

1\. Information Collected

FreeSex collects information from users at different points on the website. Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Information we collect includes:

(a) Personally Identifiable Information, which includes information that can directly identify an individual such as an individual's name, mailing address, phone number or email address. Additional personal information, such as year of birth, relationship status and sexual orientation may be added on a voluntary basis after registration, for members interested in identifying and potentially contacting other members meeting specific criteria. In order to use services (i.e. upload User Submissions, view full content) on this website, a user must create an account. During the account creation process, a user must provide Personally Identifiable Information so that we can stay in touch with our users. This information is also used to comply with any applicable laws and fulfill the duties required of our requested services. To prevent fraudulent sign ups, we may ask a user to provide financial information (such as a credit card number and its expiration date). This information may also be used for billing purposes, with the help of our business partner.

(b) IP addresses. We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to Personally Identifiable Information.

(c) Cookies. Internet browsers have a feature called cookies, which store small amounts of data on a user's computer hard drive that contains information about that user. By setting a cookie on our website, the user would not have to log in with a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our website. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our website. The only drawback to this is that the user may be limited in some areas of our website. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our website. Some of our business partners use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers); however, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

(d) Third Party Advertisers. We use third-party companies to serve advertisements when you visit our website or use our services. Third-party companies may also separately place or recognize a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

(e) Information from Third Parties. In certain circumstances, in order for our website to properly fulfill its obligation to our users, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources.

(f) Content uploaded to the site. Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Any videos that you submit to FreeSex.com may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

2\. How Information Collected Is Used

We will not knowingly use information collected on this website in ways different from what is disclosed in the Privacy Policy that is in effect. 

(a) Demographic Information. We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. The aggregated demographic information is not linked to any Personally Identifiable Information that can identify any individual person.

(b) Communicating with Our Users. We use Personally Identifiable Information (such as your name, telephone number or email address) to communicate with our users when they have questions, concerns or comments about their accounts or the services that we provide. If you contact us, we may or may not delete your emails or voicemails to us.

i) Your chosen username is displayed to other users alongside the content you upload, including videos, comments, and any private messages you send through your account. Other users can contact you through private messages.

(c) Information Shared With Third Parties. We share information with third parties in order to give our customers access to a great variety of services. Specifically, we may do the following:

(i) Use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not use Personally Identifiable Information for any use other than credit card processing; however, we will not be responsible or liable for use of the information required by credit card companies in contravention of their policies, contractual obligations or general good business procedures. 

(ii) Partner with third parties who provide services to our users. When the user signs up for or agrees to receive a specific service provided by the third party, we share the information that is needed for the third party to provide the services. 

(iii) Share your Personally Identifiable Information with other entities that are owned by FreeSex, that own FreeSex, or have some sort of corporate ownership relationship with FreeSex.

(d) Addressing Legal Issues. Further, we provide Personally Identifiable Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share Personally Identifiable Information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of FreeSex's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

(e) Sale or Transfer of FreeSex. If all or a portion of FreeSex is transferred, sold, merged, ceases operations, goes bankrupt, or is otherwise involved in a transaction where the ownership or management of FreeSex is changed (individually or collectively, a "Transaction") then your Personally Identifiable Information or other user information may be transferred or assigned to a third party as part of the Transaction.

3\. Usage by Children Under Age 18

This website is not intended for use by anyone under the age of eighteen (18) or anyone not having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet these criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of the FreeSex.com website. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who are under 18 years of age or have not attained the age of majority of their community and any individual under such age should not provide us with Personally Identifiable Information. We do not knowingly contact, market to, solicit, collect or use Personally Identifiable Information from or about any individual under the age of 18. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under the age of 18. If we are notified that we have personal information regarding a person under the age of 18 or anyone not having attained the age of majority in their community, as soon as we reasonably verify the information, we will delete their information from their account and the FreeSex.com website. However, the information may remain on a log in our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of information by children under the age of 18, please do so by emailing us at: Compliance [at] FreeSex.com.

4\. Communications from FreeSex

(a) Welcome Emails and Marketing Correspondence. We may send a welcoming email to the email address associated with the account a user has created to verify the user's password and username. This process is designed to prevent e-mail addresses from being used without permission in the creation of a FreeSex account. Established users may occasionally receive marketing material on products and services provided by FreeSex.

(b) Website and Service Updates. We send the user website and service announcement updates. Users are not permitted to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the website and/or service. We may communicate with users to provide services that users request or to discuss issues relating to their account.

(c) Contests. From time-to-time our website may request information from users via contests. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and, as such, the user has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

5\. Correcting/Updating Personal Information

Users must provide accurate and correct contact information (name, postal address, e-mail address, phone number) for their user account. If a user's Personally Identifiable Information changes (such as a zip code), they may correct and/or update such information from within their account. If further assistance is needed, please send an email request to Compliance [at] FreeSex.com.

6\. Opting Out

Users are provided an opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to the services they request. Users who no longer wish to receive certain marketing materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying and typing "unsubscribe" in the subject line in the email or by sending an email request to Compliance [at] FreeSex.com.

7\. Account Termination

If your FreeSex account is terminated or cancelled (regardless of whether it was voluntary) all of your Personally Identifiable Information will remain on our servers. Upon receipt of a written request to remove personal data, we will retain some of your information in order to prevent fraud, collect fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our other polices, address contractual issues, contact you for future marketing or promotional purposes, and comply with legal requirements. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. However, your account will be deactivated from our active, registered user database, and will only be available to select personnel.

8\. Links to Third Party Websites

This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the Privacy Policy of each and every website that collects Personally Identifiable Information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website.

9\. Security 

Users are required to keep their account passwords confidential and to not share this information with others. If you choose to reveal or share your password and FreeSex account name, we are unable to guarantee the security of your account. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to Compliance [at] FreeSex.com.

10\. Privacy Policy Changes

This Privacy Policy may change, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy that is in effect as of the time of use. You are responsible for periodically checking our Privacy Policy. You may opt-out of any posted change to our collection, use or disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information by sending an e-mail to Compliance [at] FreeSex.com. If we make minor changes to this Privacy Policy, the changes will be immediately effective upon posting the revised Privacy Policy to the website. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy or in how we will use or collect your Personally Identifiable Information, all amended terms shall automatically be effective ten (10) days after they are initially posted on the site. The date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy is the date that the Privacy Policy is effective.

11\. Privacy Policy Concerns or Questions

If you have any concern about privacy at FreeSex, please send us a thorough description to Compliance [at] FreeSex.com, and we will try to resolve it. 

Effective date: April 24, 2009
